A Guide to the William J. “Bill” Elvin Collection, 1914-2004, bulk 1963-2003
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
The William J. “Bill” Elvin Collection, 1914-2004, bulk 1963-2003
Fairfax County Public Library
MSS 06-92
31.0 linear feet
The William J. “Bill” Elvin Collection consists of 31.0 linear feet spanning the years 1914-2004 (bulk 1963-2003). The collection contains photographs, news clippings, magazine articles, correspondence, campaign materials, personal and business records, article drafts, pamphlets, reports, publications, unofficial voting returns, election mailings, meeting minutes, obituaries, notes, and brochures.
Elvin, William J. (1924-2004)
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
None
Acquisition Information
Gift of Jan Elvin, 2004
Historical and Biographical Information
William J. “Bill” Elvin was born in Dumfries, Scotland on February 15, 1918 and emigrated to Frostburg, Maryland at the age of six. He attended the University of Michigan studying political science and was an associate editor of the student newspaper The Michigan Daily. After graduating, Elvin married Jane Legge of Cumberland, Maryland and later had four children with her. In September 1942, Elvin enlisted in the Army and became an officer in the Third Army under Gen. George S. Patton. He was wounded in France in 1944, and received the Purple Heart and Silver Star.
After the war, Elvin and his family moved to Northern Virginia in 1947. Elvin worked for the Fairfax Standard from 1947-1948, and later the Washington Star for eight years. In 1956, Elvin purchased the McLean Providence Journal from founding editor Richard Smith and subsequently moved to McLean, Virginia the following year. He wrote and edited the Journal from 1956 until he sold the publication to David Dear in 1986 but remained an associate editor. Elvin retired in 1991, but bought back the paper from Dear in 1995 renaming it The McLean Times and sold it to Arcom Publishing in 1996. Elvin once again retained his associate editor title for the paper and continued to write articles until a few weeks before his death on August 26, 2004.
Throughout his life, Bill Elvin was actively involved in the McLean community as a prominent member of the McLean Lions Club, McLean Historical Society, McLean Business and Professional Association, and McLean Citizens Association. In 1996, he won the “Citizen of the Year” award for his active participation in the McLean Citizens Association. Elvin also had a profound knowledge of McLean history and heavily contributed to several historical publications.
Scope and Content
Series 1: McLean Providence Journal Subject Files, 1914-2004, Boxes 1-14
Contains the first series of subject files Elvin created during the years he owned the McLean Providence Journal and continued to maintain in later years. This series was largely unsorted and randomly arranged before processing. Some files were alphabetized by Elvin while in other cases documents never made it into a file. The files in this series have since been placed in alphabetical order. Items include news clippings, articles, article drafts, correspondence, pamphlets, obituaries, publications, unofficial voting returns, election mailings, meeting minutes, notes, brochures, and photographs. Subjects include files on McLean’s history, residents, issues, politics, organizations, and community life as well as Fairfax County government information and files on local and national elections.
Series 2: McLean Providence Journal Subject Files, 1925-2004, Boxes 15-27
Contains the second series of alphabetical McLean Providence Journal files maintained by Elvin during and after his ownership of the newspaper. Items include news clippings, notes, article drafts, publications, magazine articles, reports, election mailings, meeting minutes, brochures, obituaries and photographs. Subjects include files on McLean’s history, residents, issues, politics, organizations, and community life as well as Fairfax County government information. Of particular importance is the Ku Klux Klan file which contains photographs of the Fairfax County Klan chapter and also the only known copy of Now & Then, a Fairfax County Klan produced newspaper.
Series 3: Photographs, 1956-2003, Boxes 28-30
Photographs in this series were published in either the McLean Providence Journal, Fairfax Herald, McLean Times or used by Elvin for reference and personal purposes. The majority of the photographs in this series are undated. Those that are dated correspond to the date the photo was captured or the date they were published in Elvin’s newspapers. Subjects mainly include Fairfax County and McLean residents, politicians, buildings, and community events.
Arrangement
The files are arranged alphabetically and primarily consist of subjects relating to the history, development, politics, and community life of McLean, Virginia including the McLean Citizens Association, politicians and elections in Fairfax County, and the McLean Providence Journal.
Adjunct Descriptive Data
None
Bill Elvin’s collection of original newspapers including the complete run of the McLean Providence Journal (1944-1995) remain unprocessed and stored off-site.
Index Terms
Elvin, William J. “Bill” (1924-2004); Fairfax County - Elections; Fairfax County - Government; Fairfax County - Newspapers; Fairfax County - Politics; Fairfax Herald; McLean Citizens Association; McLean Providence Journal; McLean Times; McLean, Va.- History; McLean, Va.- Planning
Container List
- Series 1: McLean Providence Journal Subject Files, 1914-2004
  - Agricultural & Forestal, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Agriculture, 1964-1983 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Air Quality Plan - Metropolitan Washington Council of Government, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Alcohol Beverage Control and Abuse, 1975-1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Alexandria, 1978-1983 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Alternative House, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - American Campus Management Inc. - Rezoning Proposal, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - American Chemical Society, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Animals, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Annexation, 1966-1984 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Arlington Ladies, 1977-1990 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Assessments - Real Estate Tax, 1988-1992 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Baha’i Faith/ International Year of Peace, 1983-1986 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Ballantrae Rezoning, 1979-1983 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Banks, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Barry, Warren E., 1989 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Baseball - MLB Returning to DC/VA, 1991-2000 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - BDM International Inc., 1988-1993 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Becker, Theodore “Bucky”, Undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Beltway, 1990-1993 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Berger, Ernie, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Beverly Manor - Halfway House, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Billman, Tom J., 1989-1991 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Bonds - Public Works, 1978-1989 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Bose Estate / Audubon Society, 1980-1993 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Brackeen, Richard, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Builder's Buyers Guide, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Buildings - County Government Rental - Marcia Dykes Lawsuit, 1990-1993 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Burke, Kaye Sloan, Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Burling Tract Park/Scotts Run Nature Preserve, 1970-1991 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Burns Brothers Cleaners, 1983-1987 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Business Reviews - Summer '92, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Business Reviews - '93, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Cable Television, 1981-1988 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Castolaro, Daniel, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Catholics for Housing, 1987-1992 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Census - Population, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Center for Excellence in Education, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Center for Innovative Technology (CIT), 1984-1991 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Central Area Plan For McLean, VA (Draft), Undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Centreville District - A. Smith Bowman Distillery, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Centreville Historic District, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Chain Bridge Road - Improvements, 1979-1985 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Character Counts Coalition, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Chesapeake Bay Preservation Ordinance, 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Child Care, 1987-1992 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Children for the Advancement of Public Education - Daniel Goldsmith, James Newcombe, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Christian Fellowship Church, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - CIA Headquarters, 1983-2002 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - CIA Headquarters - Articles, 1955-1998 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - CIA Legal Defense Fund for Employees, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Citizens for Balanced Growth (CIT-PAC), 1992 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Citizens for Sensible Taxation - Marcia Dykes, 1991-1993 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - City of Fairfax Referendum and Annual Report, 1961-1968 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Claude Moore Colonial Farm at Turkey Run, 1973-2001 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Clean-Up McLean Campaign, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Clemyjontri Park, 2001-2003 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - The Colonies Condominium at McLean, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Colvin Run Citizens Association, Inc, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Colvin Run Mill Blacksmithing Days [contains photographs], 1981-1984 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Colvin Run Mill Park, 1969-1992 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Common Cause Lobbyists, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Commons of McLean, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Communication Towers Plan, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Community Council, 1966-1974 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Community Services Board - Mental Disabilities, 1979-1985 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Comparato, James, Undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Comprehensive Plan for Fairfax County, Virginia Area II (Draft), 1991 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Conservation - Pesticide Regulation, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Consumer Resources, 1971-1984 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Courts, 1965-1990 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Courts and Judicial, 1969-1982 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Crawford, Beverly, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Crenshaw, Craig M., 1996 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Crippen Landfill - Operation Report, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Crippen, Mark, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Crippen's Corner Development, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Culture - Fairfax County Cultural Association, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Currier/Morgan-Loman, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Defense Conversion - Impact on Virginia, 1985-1993 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - DeFusco, David, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Disaster Story - Disaster Planning, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Dolan, Bill, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Dolley Madison Boulevard - Road Widening, 1985-1990 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Dolley Madison Library, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Dominion Federal Savings - Infringement Dispute, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Downzoning, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Dranesville District, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Dranesville District Democratic Committee, 1967-1986 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Dranesville District Republican Committee, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Dranesville Supervisor Election, 1966-1987 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Dranesville Supervisor Election Clippings, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Dranesville Tavern, 1965-1993 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Driving While Intoxicated - Fairfax County Task Force on Drunk Driving, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Drugs - Ritalin, 1988-1992 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Drunk Driving - Mothers Against Drunk Driving (M.A.D.D.), 1992 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Dulles Airport, 1959-2002 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - DuVal, Clive and Susan, 1966-2002 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Economic Projections: Fairfax County, Virginia 1975-2000, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Elections - Bonds, 1988-1991 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Elections - Fairfax County voter guides, sample ballots, results, 1985-1987 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Elections - Funding, 1989-1992 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Elections - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Elections 1962, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Elections 1964, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Elections 1965, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Elections 1966, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Elections 1967, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Elections 1968, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Elections 1969, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Elections 1970, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Elections 1971, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Elections 1972, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Elections 1973, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Elections 1974, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Elections 1975, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Elections 1976, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Elections 1977, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Elections 1978, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Elections 1979, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Elections 1980, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Elections 1981, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Elections 1982, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Elections 1983, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Elections 1984, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Elections 1985, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Elections 1987, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Elections 1987 - Fairfax County Board of Supervisors Chairman, 1985-1987 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Elections 1987 - State Senate, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Elections 1988, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Elections 1988 - President, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Elections 1989, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Elections 1989 - Attorney General, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Elections 1989 - Lieutenant Governor (Don Beyer), 1989 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Elections 1990, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Elections 1990 - Fairfax County Sheriff, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Elections 1990 - U.S. Senate, 1988-1990 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Elections 1991, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Elections 1991 - Delegate (David Sanders), 1991 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Elections 1991 - District Supervisor, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Elections 1991 - Fairfax County Board of Supervisor Chairman, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Elections 1991 - Fairfax County Circuit Court Clerk, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Elections 1991 - State Senator, 1986-1991 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Elections 1992, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Elections 1992 - 8th District, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Elections 1992 - 10th District, 1988-1991 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Elections 1992 - 11th District, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Elections 1992 - Bonds, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Elections 1993, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Elections 1993 - Drainsville District Returns, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Elections 1993 - Lieutenant Governor (Mike Farris), 1993 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Elections 1994, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Elections 1995, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Elections 1996, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Elections 1997, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Elections 1998, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Elections 1999, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Elections 2000, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Elections 2001, 1999-2001 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Elections 2002, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Elections 2003, 2000-2003 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Elections 2003 - Mailings, 2000-2003 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Elections 2003 - News Clippings, 2000-2003 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Elm Street, 1987-1993 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Energy Conservation, 1975-1980 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Environmental Quality, 1971-1980 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Evans Farm Inn, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Evans Farm Inn, 1995-2001 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Fairfax Audubon Society, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Fairfax Coalition for Smarter Growth, Undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Fairfax County, 1974-2003 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Fairfax County 250th Anniversary, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Fairfax County Adult Day Health Care Associates, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Fairfax County Adult Detention Center, 1987-1990 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Fairfax County Advertised Budget Plan, 2000-2002 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Fairfax County Affirmative Action, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Fairfax County Animal Shelter, 1987-1990 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Fairfax County Assessments, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Fairfax County Board of Supervisors, 1965-1996 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Fairfax County Board of Supervisors - Budget, 1978-2000 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Fairfax County Board of Supervisors - Meeting Agendas, 2002-2003 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Fairfax County Board of Supervisors - Transition, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Fairfax County Board of Supervisors - Weekly Agenda, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Fairfax County Board of Supervisors - Weekly Agenda, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Fairfax County Board of Supervisors - Weekly Agenda, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Fairfax County Board of Supervisors - Zoning Ordinance & Planning Regulations, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Fairfax County Board of Supervisors - Zoning Proposals, 2000-2002 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Fairfax County Bonds, 1986-1992 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Fairfax County Budget, 1987-2004 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Fairfax County Chamber of Commerce [includes photographs of police officers and firefighters], 1987-1992 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Fairfax County Circuit Court, 1966-1991 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Fairfax County Citizens Handbook, 1971-2001 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Fairfax County Committee of 100, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Fairfax County Community in Action, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Fairfax County Council of the Arts, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Fairfax County Council of the PTAs, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Fairfax County Courthouse, 1979-1998 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Fairfax County Democratic Committee - The Democrat Newsletter, 1992-1994 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Fairfax County Democratic Committee - The Democrat Newsletter, 1999-2003 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Fairfax County Democrats, 1985-2000 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Fairfax County Environment, 1998-2001 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Fairfax County Federation of Citizens Association, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Fairfax County Fees, 1988-1992 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Fairfax County Fire and Rescue, 1988-1991 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Fairfax County Fire Services, 1978-2003 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Fairfax County Fire Services - Charles W. "Chuck" Colson, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Fairfax County Garage, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Fairfax County Geology, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Fairfax County Government, 1961-1973 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Fairfax County Government, 1966-1977 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Fairfax County Government Center, 1986-1990 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Fairfax County Health, 1990-2000 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Fairfax County Heritage Conservatory, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Fairfax County Historical Landmarks Preservation Commission, 1966-1970 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Fairfax County History, 1962-2001 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Fairfax County Housing, 1975-1990 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Fairfax County Housing - United Way, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Fairfax County Human Services, 1985-1999 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Fairfax County Infill, 2000-2002 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Fairfax County Jail, 1976-1993 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Fairfax County Libraries, 1987-1994 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Fairfax County Master Plan, 1961-1990 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Fairfax County National Bank, Undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Fairfax County Office For Women & Commission For Women- Divorce Information, 1993-1995 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Fairfax County Overtime Pay, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Fairfax County Park Authority, 1980-2001 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Fairfax County Park Authority and Land Preservation, 2001-2004 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Fairfax County Parkway, 1988-1992 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Fairfax County Planning Commission, 1965-2002 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Fairfax County Police, 1964-2002 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Fairfax County Police - Crime News Clippings, 1987-2001 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Fairfax County Public Information and Internet, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Fairfax County Republicans, 1965-1999 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Fairfax County Roadside Litter, 1978-1982 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Fairfax County School Board, 1998-2004 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Fairfax County Schools, 1973-1978 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Fairfax County Schools - Statistics and Reports, 1964-1998 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Fairfax County Taxes, 1966-2002 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Fairfax County Technology, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Fairfax County Water Authority, 1967-2002 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Fairfax Courthouse, 1966-1983 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - The Fairfax Newsletter, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Fairfax ReLeaf, Undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Fairview Park, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Farley, Guy O., 1998 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - First Financial of Virginia Corporation/ First American Bank of Virginia, 1975-1983 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Foust, John W., 2002 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - General Kinetics Inc., 1968 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Georgetown Pike, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Golden vs. Ramapo, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Graham, Katherine, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Great Falls Ecumenical Council, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Great Falls Nike Park, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Growth, 1973-1999 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Hamilton Bank and Trust Company, Undated (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Herrera, Anita, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Horse Power - Karen Washburn, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Hunting Ridge - Rezoning Proposal, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - ICL Inc., 1978 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Kingman, Mary, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Land Zoning Planning Policy, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - League of Women Voters of the Fairfax Area, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Lewinsville Park - Field Improvements, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Lind, Howie, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Lindberg, Carolyn, Undated (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Lynch, Frank J., 1987 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Lynwood - Pond Cleanup, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Madison Homes - Rezoning Proposal, 1998-2000 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Major Findings of Population Growth, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - McLean Bible Church, 2001-2004 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - McLean Business and Professional Association, 1975-1999 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - McLean Capital Improvement, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - McLean Central Business District - Comprehensive Plan, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - McLean Central Business District - Final Draft Plan, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - McLean Chamber of Commerce, 1997-2003 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - McLean Chamber of Commerce, 1986-2000 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - McLean Chamber of Commerce - Publications, 1997-2003 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - McLean Church of Christ, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - McLean Citizens Advisory Council, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - McLean Citizens Association, 1951-1953 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - McLean Citizens Association, 1962-1969 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - McLean Citizens Association, 1975-1978 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - McLean Citizens Association, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - McLean Citizens Association, 1981-1989 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - McLean Citizens Association, 1991-1994 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - McLean Citizens Association, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - McLean Citizens Association, 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - McLean Citizens Association - Board of Directors, 1980-1989 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - McLean Citizens Association - Board of Directors Handbook, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - McLean Citizens Association - General Membership Meeting Agendas and Minutes, 1980-1989 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - McLean Citizens Association - History, Undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - McLean Citizens Association - Jarvis/Schiller Cluster Development, 1986-1989 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - McLean Citizens Association - Master Plan for McLean Commercial Area, 1961-1968 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - McLean Citizens Association - McLean Central Area Plan, 1963-1973 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - McLean Citizens Association - McLean Letter, 1981-1984 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - McLean Citizens Association - McLean Project for the Arts, 1986-1989 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - McLean Citizens Association - News Clippings, 1982-2000 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - McLean Citizens Association - Nominating Committee, 1980-1994 (Box 8, Folder 22)